Guide to the Robert M. Solow Papers, 1951-2011 and undated RL.01230
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Professional Service Series, 1961-1986, 567303; 9 boxes
  - American Economic Association (Folders 1-3 of 14), 567330 (Box 79)
  - American Economic Association, 567329; Folders 4-12 of 14 (Box 80)
  - American Economic Association, 567328; Folders 13-14 of 14 (Box 81)
  - The Beijer Institute, 567327; 4 folders (Box 81)
  - Commission on Income Maintenance, 567326; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 81)
  - Commission on Income Maintenance, 567325; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 82)
  - Committee for Economic Development, 567324 (Box 82)
  - Cornell University Department of Economics, 567323; 4 folders (Box 82)
  - Eastern Economic Association, 567322; Folders 1-3 of 4 (Box 82)
  - Eastern Economic Association, 567321; Folder 4 of 4 (Box 83)
  - Econometrica, 567320 (Box 83)
  - Economic Skit Parties, 567319 (Box 83)
  - Federal Reserve Bank of Boston, 567318 (Box 83)
  - Full Employment Steering Committee, 567317 (Box 83)
  - Future US Economic Growth (FUSEG), 567316; 5 folders (Box 83)
  - The Institute for Advanced Study (Princeton), 567315; Folders 1-8 of 11 (Box 84)
  - The Institute for Advanced Study, 567314; Folders 9-11 of 11 (Box 85)
  - Joint Economics Committee, 567313 (Box 85)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 567312 (Box 85)
  - National Bureau of Economic Research, 567311; Folders 1-3 of 10 (Box 85)
  - National Bureau of Economic Research, 567310; Folders 4-10 of 10 (Box 86)
  - National Science Foundation, 567309; Folder 1 of 3 (Box 86)
  - National Science Foundation, 567308; Folders 2-3 of 3 (Box 87)
  - Society of Fellows (Harvard), 567307 (Box 87)
  - University of Massachusetts: Dep. of Economics Development, 567306; 2 folders (Box 87)
  - University of Massachusetts: Visiting Committee, 567305; 2 folders (Box 87)
  - Woods Hole Oceanographic Institution, 567304 (Box 87)
- Audiovisual Series, 2003-2009, 567298; 1 box
  Series consists of four audio visual recordings featuring Solow. Recording labeled "Professor Samuelson and Professor Solow on Professor Franco Modigliani" is on a VHS cassette. The other materials are in DVD format.
  Conditions Governing Access note
  [Original audiovisual materials are closed to use. Use of these materials may require production of listening or viewing copies. Please contact Research Services before coming to use this collection.]
  - Professor Samuelson and Professor Solow on Professor Franco Modigliani, 2003, 567302 (Box 109)
  - Keynes and the Cambridge Keynesians: A 'revolution in economics' to be accomplished, Intervento di Robert Solow, 2008, 567301 (Box 109)
  - Addicted to Money with David McWilliams, 2009, 567300 (Box 109)
  - MOT: More Money to the US Rich, NTSC, 2009, 567299 (Box 109)